{"head":"Mustafa Umit Oner","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"Singapore","rank":38,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have scientists that have collaborated with Mustafa Umit Oner on research projects?","answers":[{"text":"Singapore","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":0}
{"head":"Ming Lin","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United States","rank":6,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have institutions that have hosted Ming Lin for research collaborations?","answers":[{"text":"United States","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":1}
{"head":"Xinggang Wang","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"China","rank":18,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"What are the countries that Xinggang Wang has collaborated with through their institution?","answers":[{"text":"China","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":2}
{"head":"Zhiyu Tan","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United States","rank":6,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have institutions that have funded research projects led by Zhiyu Tan?","answers":[{"text":"United States","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":3}
{"head":"Jianqiang Yao","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"China","rank":18,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"What are the countries that Jianqiang Yao has published research papers in?","answers":[{"text":"China","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":4}
{"head":"Yuanjun Gao","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United States","rank":6,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have institutions that have hosted Yuanjun Gao for research collaborations?","answers":[{"text":"United States","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":5}
{"head":"Giambattista Parascandolo","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"Finland","rank":22,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"What are the countries that Giambattista Parascandolo has published research papers in?","answers":[{"text":"Finland","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":6}
{"head":"Boris Borisenko","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"Russian Federation","rank":36,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"What are the countries that Boris Borisenko has published research papers in?","answers":[{"text":"Russian Federation","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":7}
{"head":"Petko Georgiev","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United Kingdom","rank":12,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"What are the countries that Petko Georgiev has published research papers in?","answers":[{"text":"United Kingdom","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":8}
{"head":"Sang Michael Xie","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United States","rank":6,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have institutions that have funded research projects led by Sang Michael Xie?","answers":[{"text":"United States","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":9}
{"head":"Cian Eastwood","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United Kingdom","rank":12,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have scientists that have collaborated with Cian Eastwood on research projects?","answers":[{"text":"United Kingdom","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":10}
{"head":"Shusen Wang","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United States","rank":6,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have institutions that have funded research projects led by Shusen Wang?","answers":[{"text":"United States","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":11}
{"head":"Bryan Hooi","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"Singapore","rank":38,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"What are the countries that Bryan Hooi has published research papers in?","answers":[{"text":"Singapore","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":12}
{"head":"Hado van Hasselt","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"United Kingdom","rank":12,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"Which countries have scientists that have collaborated with Hado van Hasselt on research projects?","answers":[{"text":"United Kingdom","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":13}
{"head":"Christos Louizos","relation_a":"belongs_to","relation_b":"located_in","ans":"Netherlands","rank":31,"uncertainty":0,"prompt":"What are the countries that Christos Louizos has collaborated with through their institution?","answers":[{"text":"Netherlands","confidence":0}],"text_query_id":14}
